Will this make you feel good?
これ気持ちよくしてくれる?
Yeah.
うん
First try touching it with your hands.
最初2人で手で触ってみて
Try stroking it.
な でなでしてみて
Sakura-chan.
さくらちゃん
Can you say that?
それ喋ってもらえる?
Spit on me.
ツバでびしゃぶしゃなで
Use your tongue a lot.
いっぱいベロつかっておいて
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Too bad.
がっかい
Talk a lot.
いっぱい喋って
Because I put a lot of spit on it and jerked off.
ツバいっぱいつけてシコシコしたから
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Now, fill up your tickets.
さぁ、きっぷいっぱいつけて
Erotic?
エロい?
Yeah.
うん
Sakura-chan, you've messed up.
さくらちゃん、もっかいしちゃって
When it's full of spit, I jerk it off.
ツバいっぱいたらシコシコって
Even two people can take the tongue.
2人でもベロとって
Either way, talk a little bit.
どっちかちんちんしゃべって
Bring your face closer.
顔近づけてほら
It's ticking, dick.
かちかちだね、ちんちん
I don't feel like it yet.
気持ちはまだだよ
Do you want to work with these guys?
こいつらの手をやっていきたい?
Sakura-chan, please jerk off like that.
さ くらちゃん、そうやってシコシコしてあげて
Yeah.
うん
It got really stiff.
シコシコになっちゃってね
Have you become stiff?
シコシコになっちゃった?
It has amazing qualities.
すごい性質ついてるね